So Carrie, in lesson one, we talked about how the size in experiment
Carrie 在第一课中
based on your practical significance, your statistical significance and
我们谈到如何根据实际显著性、统计显著性以及
the sensitivity you want.
你所需的敏感性来确定实验的规模
What do we need to update about that based on what we've covered since then?
根据最近我们学习的内容 你要对此补充些什么吗？
>> Well, we have a couple of things that we've just looked at.
我们最近讨论了几个问题
Your choice of metric, your choice of the unit of diversion, and
包括如何选择指标、分组单元
your choice of population.
以及总体
And all those things can affect the variability of your metric.
这些问题都可影响指标的差异性
So you want to take all the stuff into account and then start to determine
所以你得考虑所有这些方面
the size based on the process that we talked about before.
然后再根据之前学习的过程来确定实验规模
And then you're going to have to figure out if what you've planned to do is
你还得考虑实验持续时间和指标差异性
really realistic, given how long you have to run the experiment and
并弄清楚你想分析的事情
the variability of your metrics.
是否有可能实现
>> Okay. Can you give me an example?
你能举例说明吗？
>> Well let's think about what we talked about before.
我们以之前讨论过的例子为例
The page load time, the 90th percentile latency.
页面加载时间 90% 的延迟
Now originally you could measure that in an event-based
你最初可能使用基于事件的分组方式来进行衡量
diversion because you just measure each page load time.
因为你只要衡量每个页面的加载时间
But let's say we now say, okay, we also want to look at a user ID
现在 我们假设还要使用基于用户 ID 的分组方式
diversion where we look at whether that user uses our site more or
来了解用户体验到的延迟
less based on the latency that they're experiencing.
是否会影响其使用我们网站的频率
Now that's a little more challenging as a metric,
这个指标更有挑战性
because you're going to need a fair amount of user data to make that work.
因为你需要获得大量用户数据才能分析出这个指标
And if you're originally planning to run this globally, you may realize looking
如果你最初想要在全局层面执行这个实验
at the variance of your metrics, that that's just not really realistic.
那么你可能会发现观察指标方差不太现实
It's going to take a very long time to get a lot of data,
你需要很长时间才能获得大量数据
it's a big investment.
这样的话 投资太大了
So you may want to go back and say, you know what?
你可能会回头告诉我
I'm really affecting the 90th percentile here, that's what I'm targeting.
我很在意这个 90% 这是我的关注目标
So, let's look at people with slow connections.
我们可以观察连接缓慢的用户
And then maybe, because I need to get enough data, I want to look at a cohort
因为我需要获得足够数据
of users who've used my site fairly regularly over the past two months.
所以我想要关注最近两个月经常使用我的网站的用户队列
And that way, I can get more data about them more quickly.
从而我可以更快地获得更多有关他们的数据
And so, while this restriction may give you a smaller scope to your project,
虽然这个限制会使得实验范围缩小
it can really give you a better sense of whether you're going to get
但在实际投入时间执行大规模实验之前
a signal out of this experiment at all before you invest the time and
它能帮助你弄清楚
the user time in actually running a much larger experiment.
你能否从实验中获得见解